bbq-book.com 2016-11-06

# Privacy Policy | Barbecue Recipes | Barbecue Cookbook | Competition BBQ Secrets

Privacy Policy

**Network 6000, Inc. Privacy Policy**

Thank you for visiting Network 6000, Inc.'s ("Network 6000") personal data management and e-commerce Internet web site ("Site") located at the URLs www.network6000.com, www.network6000.biz, www.network6000.net, www.electricitybook.com, www.bbq-book.biz, and www.bbq-book.com. This Privacy Policy details certain policies implemented throughout Network 6000 governing Network 6000's use of personally identifiable information provided to Network 6000 via this Site.

**Privacy Policy Updates**

Due to the Internet's rapidly evolving nature, Network 6000 may need to update this Privacy Policy from time to time.  If so, Network 6000 will post its updated Privacy Policy on our Site located at the sites mentioned in paragraph one so you are always aware of what personally identifiable information we may collect and how we may use this information.  Network 6000 encourages you to review this Privacy Policy regularly for any changes. Your continued use of this Site will be subject to the then-current Privacy Policy.

**Information Collection and Use**

You can generally visit our Site without revealing any personally identifiable information about yourself.  However, in certain sections of this Site, to use certain services, we may require you to register for an account, or we may invite you to submit questions or comments or request information, participate in surveys, questionnaires or contests, subscribe to newsletters or participate in community forums.  Due to the nature of some of these activities, we may ask that you complete and submit an online form with personally identifiable information such as your name, username, email address, contact information and credit card information.  We may use your personally identifiable information to deliver certain services, products or information you have requested, verify your authority to enter certain password protected areas of the Site, send you notices for products and/or services that you have used or that may be of interest to you, and improve the content and general administration of the Site.  If you are a registered user and post to any of the Sites community forums, other registered users of this Site may view your username and may send you emails, but they will not be able to see your actual email address.  We may use your personally identifiable information to send you advertisements and other promotional information regarding our products and services or the products and services of our third party marketing partners and other communications related to the Site. 

**Children's Privacy**

Network 6000 recognizes the privacy interests of children and we encourage parents and guardians to take an active role in their children's online activities and interests.  No personally identifiable information is collected by Network 6000 and Network 6000's services and Site are not intended for children under the age of 13.  Network 6000 does not target its services or this Site to children under 13.  Network 6000 does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13.

**Cookies**

We may use small text files called cookies to improve overall Site experience. A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's hard drive containing information about the user. Cookies generally do not permit us to personally identify you.  Cookies must be enabled for you to use certain areas of the Site.

Advertisements that appear on this Site are delivered to users by our advertising partners. Our advertising partners may download cookies to your computer. Doing this allows the advertising network to recognize your computer each time they send you an advertisement. In this way, they may compile information about where you, or others who are using your computer, saw their advertisements and determine which advertisements are clicked. This information allows an advertising network to deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. Network 6000 does not have access to or control of the cookies that may be placed by the third party advertisers.

We may use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

**Aggregate Information**

The Site may track the total number of visitors to our Site, the number of visitors to each page of our Site, IP addresses, External Web Sites (defined below) linked to, and we may analyze this data for trends and statistics in the aggregate, but such information will be maintained, used and disclosed in aggregate form only and it will not contain personally identifiable information. We may use such aggregate information to analyze trends, administer the Site, track users' movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use.  We may share this aggregate information with third parties to assist them in targeting advertisements to appropriate audiences.

**Disclosure**

We may provide your personally identifiable information that we collect and the data generated by cookies to the vendors and service agencies that we may engage to assist us. For example, we may provide your personally identifiable information to an organization in order to complete a service (e.g., process your payment).  We will also disclose your personally identifiable information if we reasonably believe we are required to do so by law, regulation or other government authority.  We will not sell your personally identifiable information to any other company or organization except we may transfer your personally identifiable information to a successor entity upon a merger, consolidation or other corporate reorganization in which Network 6000 participates or to a purchaser of all or substantially all of Network 6000's assets to which this Site relates. 

**Links to Third Party Sites**

The Site may provide links to other Web sites or resources over which Network 6000 does not have control ("External Web Sites").  Such links do not constitute an endorsement by Network 6000 of those External Web Sites.  You acknowledge that Network 6000 is providing these links to you only as a convenience, and further agree that Network 6000 is not responsible for the content of such External Web Sites.  Your use of External Web Sites is subject to the terms of use and privacy policies located on the linked to External Web Sites.

**Security**

We may employ procedural and technological measures, consistent with industry practice.  Such measures are reasonably designed to help protect your personally identifiable information from loss, unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration or destruction.  Network 6000 may use encryption, secure socket layer, firewalls, internal restrictions, password protection and other security measures to help prevent unauthorized access to your personally identifiable information.

**Correction/Updating Personally Identifiable Information**

Network 6000 provides you with the ability to review, correct and delete any of the personally identifiable information that you have provided to us.  If you wish to review or correct any information you have provided to us, [you may access your account and review, correct and delete your personally identifiable information] [or you may contact us by email at: affiliate @ network6000.com (spaces inserted to avoid spam - do not type them).] If you have any questions regarding this Privacy Policy please contact us by the [link- contact us page] or via email at:  affiliate @ network6000.com (spaces inserted to avoid spam - do not type them).

This Privacy Policy was last updated: Sept 23, 2009  
This Privacy Policy is effective as of: Sept 12, 2006
